Daniel Rafique - Blockchain & Web3 Developer

• Interested in: Blockchain Web3 development

• Currently building: Automated Market Maker for Solana

• Looking to collaborate on: Web3 projects

• Reach me on: Telegram

 $\textbf{Fullstack Developer} \mid \text{eCommerce} \mid \text{Blockchain} \mid \text{AI/ML} \mid \text{Cloud Administration}$

Location: South West London, UK

Email: koynlabs@gmail.com

Website: koynlabs.com - COMING SOON

About Me

I am a **Blockchain and Web3 Developer** based in London, specializing in decentralized technologies and solutions. With over 20 years of experience in web development, my journey began with HTML and CSS in 2003, quickly advancing to PHP and MySQL by 2006. Over the years, I have evolved from building websites to developing sophisticated eCommerce solutions, culminating in my current focus on the blockchain space.

I'm experinced in PHP, JavaScript, and frameworks such as: Docker, Web3JS, ReactJS, and NodeJS. My current focus areas include API integrations, Blockchain technology, and AI/ML.

Professional Experience

Co-Founder - Koynlabs

July 2024 - ongoing

Visit Website

- Developed automated market making software for Solana SPL-tokens using **Docker**, **JavaScript**, **Nginx**, and **Websockets**. The bot is accessible through Telegram.

Creator - ANGRY PIG Solana Memecoin

May 2024 - Aug 2024

Visit Website

- Created the Angry Pig Solana memecoin and NFT collection. Check out the Twitter and Telegram links on the website. **Raydium**, **Dexscreener**, **Dextools**.

Founder - WAVETRADER (discontinued)

May 2023 - Oct 2023

Visit Website

- Developed an automated cryptocurrency trading service with **Java 8**, **NodeJS**, **MongoDB**, and **ReactJS**.

Backend Developer - SuperPayments.com

May 2022 - June 2022

Visit Website

- Optimized and refined Magento 2 extensions for Black Friday/Cyber Monday using **PHP**, **Knockout JS**, and **XML**.

Integration Specialist - DMMC NFT Platform

Jan 2021 - May 2021

- Integrated Blockchain and NFT Metadata into Hubspot CRM using **NodeJS**, **PM2**, and **Moralis**.

Backend Developer - Vision Direct

July 2020 - Sep 2020

Visit Website

- Backend Magento development, including feature development, bug fixes, and upgrades for Magento 1.

Technologies & Tools

- Languages: PHP, JavaScript, Java, SQL
- Frameworks: Magento 1 & 2, Laravel, ReactJS, NodeJS, Web3js, Solana, Metaplex, Moralis
- Blockchain: Solana, Ethereum
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Firestore
- DevOps: GIT, CI/CD, Docker

Education

• BSc in Business & Economics - Oxford Brookes University & Open University

Previous Experience Magento, Laravel

Kurt Geiger Migration

- Led a successful migration from Magento 1 to Magento 2, ensuring seamless transition and improved performance.
- Technologies used: GIT, PHP7.2, MySQL, XML & JSON, JavaScript KnockoutJS, Microservices, NodeJS, REST

Pay360 Extension Rebuild

- Rewrote the Magento 2 extension to work with the latest version, improving functionality and performance.
- Technologies used: GIT, PHP7.2, MySQL, XML & JSON, JavaScript KnockoutJS

IBM - Audi

March 2018 - June 2018

- M2 Transition project through to delivery for Audi.co.uk.
- **Technologies used:** PHP7.0, MySQL, XML & JSON, JavaScript KnockoutJS, Microservices, Adobe AEM

Condenast for Style.com

 $July\ 2016$ - $December\ 2016$

- Magento Development contract for Style.com M1 Marketplace Extension refactor and M2 Marketplace Extension development.
- Technologies used: GIT, PHP7.0, MySQL, XML & JSON, Zend Client

Klarna AB (UK Office)

October 2015 - June 2016

- Magento Development contract for Klarna AB. Merchant integration and customization of the official Klarna Checkout Extension.
- Technologies used: GIT, PHP5.6 7.0, MySQL, XML & JSON

Starbucks

February 2014 - March 2014

- Frontend Development for Starbucks B2B portal website.
- Technologies used: GIT, PHP5.6, MySQL, XML & JSON, Laravel

And countless other startups, SME's and enterprise level builds that I've helped to bugfix and or develop from scratch.

Certifications

• Magento Certified Developer

Contact Me

- LinkedIn: Daniel Rafique
- **GitHub:** github.com/Daniel-Rafique
- Telegram: [@KoynLabsDev](https://t.me/KoynLabsDev)
- Twitter: [@koynlabs](https://twitter.com/koynlabs)

Let's build something amazing together!

• Download the PDF version of this README